const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "2.3",
    title: "Wh questions + Present Simple",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "Kto?",
    back: "Who?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co?",
    back: "What?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego?",
    back: "Why?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy?",
    back: "When?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie?",
    back: "Where?",
  },
  {
    front: "Który?/ Która?",
    back: "Which?",
  },
  {
    front: "Jak?",
    back: "How?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kto to jest?",
    back: "Who is this?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kim jesteś?",
    back: "Who are you?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kogo lubisz najbardziej?",
    back: "Who do you like the most?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kogo ona lubi?",
    back: "Who does she like?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co to jest?",
    back: "What is it?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co chcesz kupić?",
    back: "What do you want to buy?",
  },
  {
    front: "Czego on potrzebuje?",
    back: "What does he need?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego jesteś smutny?",
    back: "Why are you sad?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego jest zmęczony?",
    back: "Why is he tired?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego tu pracujesz?",
    back: "Why do you work here?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy są twoje urodziny?",
    back: "When is your birthday?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy jesteś wolny?\nKiedy jesteś wolna?",
    back: "When are you free?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy kończą pracę?",
    back: "When do they finish work?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie ja jestem?",
    back: "Where am I?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie jesteś?",
    back: "Where are you?",
  },
  {
    front: "Skąd jesteś?",
    back: "Where are you from?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie to jest?",
    back: "Where is it?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie mieszkasz?",
    back: "Where do you live?",
  },
  {
    front: "Którą książkę chcesz?",
    back: "Which book do you want?",
  },
  {
    front: "Którą restaurację lubisz?",
    back: "Which restaurant do you like?",
  },
  {
    front: "Które miejsce wolisz?",
    back: "Which place do you prefer?",
  },
  {
    front: "Jak się masz?",
    back: "How are you?",
  },
  {
    front: "Ile masz lat?",
    back: "How old are you?",
  },
];

export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
